
const jsondata = {
    "Topics": [
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health and Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessing"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health and Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Method"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health and Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Symbols"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Tolerance"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Pulleys and Belts"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Lubricant"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Retention"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Torquing"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets and Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets and Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Filtration"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Measuring"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Power"
        },
        {
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Type"
        }
    ],
    "QB": [
        {
            "Question ID2": "29",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each description to the equivalent pictorial representation ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Dead Blow Hammer                                                B) Ball Peen Hammer                                                   C) Claw Hammer                                                          D) Sledge Hammer",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                     B)                                                          C)                                                               D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question1",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "42",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Symbols",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match the projection angle to the correct symbol",
            "Answer alternatives": "A)                                                                                  B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question2",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "60",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each description to the equivalent pictorial representation ",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question1",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "62",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Torquing",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The flange nuts in the following diagram require to be tightened, provide a typical torqueing sequence if there was no guidance available ",
            "Attachment(s)": "Question3",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "64",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each description to the equivalent pictorial representation ",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question6",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "65",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each function description to the respective thread type",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question4",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "69",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each description to the equivalent pictorial representation ",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question7",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "96",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each description to the equivalent pictorial representation ",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question1",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "120",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The pictorials indicate types of coupling misalignment, match sketch to type",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question1",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "122",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each picture to the respective Drive belt",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question2",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "125",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each picture to the respective drive chain",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question3",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "126",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each picture to the respective drive gears",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question4",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "130",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Identify each of the bearing components from the exploded diagram",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question1",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "131",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Match each picture to the respective bearing ",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-Question2",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "195",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using the attached spline ring gauge sketch, advise what is (A) and what is (B)",
            "Answer alternatives": "A)                                                                              B)",
            "Correct Answer": "A) Go Gauge                                                                 B) No-Go Gauge",
            "Attachment(s)": "SplineRings",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "208",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using the sketch Gear Train Ratio, drag and drop the correct answer to the three questions to determine the correct gear ratios.",
            "Answer alternatives": "0.29:1                                                                         0.35:1                                                                         0.66:1                                                                              1.50:1                                                                         2.85:1                                                                          4.27:1",
            "Correct Answer": "Question 1) 2.85:1                                  Question 2) 1.5:1                                   Question 3) 4.27:1",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-GearTrainRatio",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "210",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using the attached sketch, match the identification letter to the types of keys",
            "Correct Answer": "A) Square Key.                 B) Flat Key.                       C) Dowel.                          D) Feather Key.                  E) Woodruff Key.                   F) Gib-Head Key.                      D) Tapered Key.",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-KeyTypes",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "213",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using the sketch Transmission Gear Train Ratio, darag and drop the answer to both questions to determine the correct gear ratios.",
            "Answer alternatives": "1 to 1.53                                                                      1 to 1.02                                                                   2.03 to 1                                                                      1 to 0.97                                                                      0.49 to 1                                                                                                                                                  1.35 to 1                                                                  2.65 to 1",
            "Correct Answer": "Question 1) 1 to 1.02                                  Question 2) 2.03 to 1",
            "Attachment(s)": "DriveComponents-Type-QX.213-TransmissionGearTrainRatio.pdf",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "214",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using the sketch Lubrication Schematic, identify the correct description to the correct item ballon",
            "Answer alternatives": "A)\r\nB)\r\nC)\r\nD)\r\nE)\r\nF)\r\nG)\r\nH)",
            "Correct Answer": "1) Pump.                            2) Safety Relief Valve.                   3) Motor.                                              4) Pressure Gauge.                            5) Filter.                                           6) Pressure Gauge.                              7) Pressure Transmitter.                      8) Heat Exchanger.",
            "Attachment(s)": "Lubrication-Method-QX.214-LubricationSchematic-question.pdf",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "215",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Drag and Drop",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using the sketch \"Types of Gears\" select the correct types of gears for \"A\", \"B\" and \"C\".",
            "Answer alternatives": "Spur Gears.                                                                Helical Gears.                                                                                  Herringbone Gears.",
            "Correct Answer": "A) Spur Gears.                          B) Helical Gears.                                    C) Herringbone Gears.",
            "Attachment(s)": "Images-TypesofGears",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "3",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The correct posture for lifting a 10kg load from the ground is",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Bent knees, straight back and load as close to the body as possible.                                                         B) The easiest method possible.                                        C) Bent knees, straight back and load clamped between palms.                                                                                D) Bent back and straight knees with fingers under the load.",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife",
            "Approved For Articulate?": "Ok",
            "Added to Articulate": "Ok",
            "Pedagogic Approved": "Ok",
            "Approved in Articulate": "Ok",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "1",
            "Added to Articulate2": "1",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "1",
            "Approved in Articulate2": "1"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "4",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the reason why an isolation should have a locking mechanism.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Permit LOTO \r\nB) Prevent operation\r\nC) For secondary safety                                            D) All of the above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "6",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "After identifying the risks in a risk assessment, what should be the next step",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Highlight the risks\r\nB) Stop the job\r\nC) Carry on with the job                                              D) Reduce the risk and re-assess",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "8",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When recording exposure to HAV (Hand - Arm Vibration) what is the dimensioning factor for allowed exposure?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Time of exposure (Frequency)                                                        B) Tool vibration\r\nC) PPE\r\nD) Tool condition ",
            "Correct Answer": "\r\nA)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "9",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "During the Permit to work issue, you need to perform the risk assessment. What is the main goal of a Risk assessment?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Evalluate the risks in the specific task that you are going to do.                                                                                                                                  B) Check if you have all resources to do the job.           C) Check if the tools and PPE you going to use are in good condition.                                                           D) All above.      ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "10",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the goal of Risk Assessment Matrix?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Classify the hazards                                                B) Identify the hazards.                         \r\nC) identify the probablity of hazards occur.                                D) All above.",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "11",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In some instances it is impossible to use the available tools to do a specific task / maintenance. In this case how should you proceed.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Request tools from you supervisor.\r\nB) Modify the available tool to do the task\r\nC) Research for correct tool and request it from your supervisor.\r\nD) All of the Above",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "12",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The employees that need Lock out / Tag out training are?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Authorized Employees\r\nB) Affected Employees\r\nC) Office employees\r\nD) All employees",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "20",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Choose what type of hammer you would choose for bearing and dowel pin assembly:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Dead Blow Hammer\r\nB) Brass hammer\r\nC) Both hammers can be used.",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "21",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Choose the best suited hammer for installing0 item M05 in drawing D1139-A0068. See drawing ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Sledge Hammer\r\nB) Dead Blow Hammer\r\nC) Claw Hammer\r\nD) All above can be used for seal seating",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Tools-Hand-QX.21-SealDataSheet.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "26",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "You need to drill a hole to tap a threaded hole of M11 x 1,50 mm. Which Drill bit is correct according to the size.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) The correct drill is 9.5 mm\r\nB) The correct measure is 3/8\"  \r\nC) Both are correct",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Tools-Hand-QX.26-Drillchart.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "27",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Measuring",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Why is it important to work with calibrated tools?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) To assure you are getting the correct value.\r\nB) For customer check the tool.\r\nC) To keep the measuring error within certain level.\r\nD) A and C are correct.",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "28",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Measuring",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When should you calibrate your measuring device?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) According to recommendation of the manufacturer.\r\nB) After any mechanical or electrical shock.\r\nC)  Periodically according the specific standards ( API, ISO)\r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "30",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "During selection of a hand tool to carry out a specific task, it should be inspected for",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Applicability, Operation and safety\r\nB) Operation, Brand and integrity\r\nC) Calibration, Brand and condition",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "33",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Measuring",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "For measuring an external diameter to an accuracy of 0.001” select suitable measuring devices",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Tape Measure\r\nB) Rule                                                                        C) Micrometer                                                                ",
            "Correct Answer": "C)                                                    ",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "37",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Which thread tap should be used when starting threading a hole?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Taper Tap\r\nB) Intermediate Tap\r\nC) Bottom Tap",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "40",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Symbols",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "From drawing number 30182280, sheet 2, cell, A8. Confirm function and purpose for the symbol.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) All dimensions referenced have tolerance of 0.030”\r\nB) Parallel to \"B\" within 0.030\"                                      C) Total runout tolerance within 0.030”\r\nD) Diagonal tolerance of 0.030”",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Symbols-QX.40-30182280revVsheet2-cellA8.pdf",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "41",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Tolerance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Given a base measurement of 18.63” confirm the upper and lower acceptable dimension. Ref drawing number 30182280 title box",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 18.92” – 18.32”\r\nB) 18.62” +/- 1/16”\r\nC) 18.72” – 18.52”                                                                 D) 18.60\" - 18.66\"",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Symbols-QX.40-30182280revVsheet2-cellA8.pdf",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "45",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Reference drawing number M614002425-ASM-001 sheet 14, Identify typical loading on the shaft assembly",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Axial only\r\nB) Radial only                                                                              C) Axial and Radial\r\nD) Downward",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Fundamentals-QX.44-M614002425-ASM-001rev23.pdf",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "46",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Drawing revision control is critical for what reason",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) To document when the drawing was made in color                 B) To record drawing changes \r\nC) To avoid engineering changes\r\nD) To control dimensions",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "47",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Tolerance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The purpose of a dimensional tolerance is to",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Provide limits on a base dimention                            B) Provide a basis for BOM\r\nC) Maintain component in Glovia\r\nD) Voiding component warranty",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "49",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the scale of drawing 30177192?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 1:2\r\nB) 0.500\r\nC) 0.200\r\nD) 1:5",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Fundamentals-QX.49-30177192-ASMrevP.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "50",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "According to the drawing 6316-0035-10, the last revision is ___. The modification in the drawing in this revision was to _____.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) C; add the details D and E\r\nB) B; add the details E and F\r\nC) A; add 4.00 diameter dimension\r\nD) B; add 4.00 diameter dimension",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Interpret-QX.50-6316-0035-10revB.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "52",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The note shown in the zone C2 of page 4 on the Drawing relates to:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) The Shot pin pressure should be adjusted between 450 to 650 psi.\r\nB) The pressure switch set point is denoted 2500 psi.\r\nC) The pressure is set according commissioning procedure",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Interpret-QX.52-30181083-SCHrevT.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "53",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Symbols",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The symbol shown in the Drawing 10659959-DAD zone C2 is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) The parallelism of surface should be 0.002\" with surface A\r\nB) Concentricy should be 0.002\" with diameter A\r\nC) The perpendicularity should be 0.002\" with surface A\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Symbols-QX.53-10659959-DADrev5.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "54",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Tolerance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In the drawing OC3932KM02-S2001, section A-A, the concentricity, Flatness and parallelism values are respectfully:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 0,5;0,3;0,5.\r\nB) 0,5; 0,3; 0,1.\r\nC) 0,5; 0,1;0,1.\r\nD) 0,1; 0,5;0,3.",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Tolerance-QX.54-OC3932KM02-S2001-Rev.6.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "55",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In the drawing 10659959-DAD, what information is showed in the zone D4?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Drill 17/32\" hole, 1-7/16\" deep, 5/8\" UNC-3B, TAP 15/16\" DEEP\r\nB) Drill 17/32\" hole throught, 5/8\" UNC-3B TAP 1\" DEEP\r\nC) Drill 49/64\" hole, 2\" deep, 5/8\" UNC-3B TAP 1-5/8\" DEEP\r\nD) Drill 17/32\" hole, 1.56\" deep, 5/8\"-11 UNC-3B, TAP 1-1/4\" DEEP",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Interpret-QX.55-10659959-DADrev5.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "56",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In the drawing 118632-ASM, what is showed in the zone D8? ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) The Drawing Label\r\nB) The drawing Notes\r\nC) The grip Jaw Cylinder\r\nD) The manifold with valves",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Interpret-QX.56-118632-ASMrevD.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "57",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Advise what type of drawing this is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Manufacturing drawing\r\nB) Assembly Drawing\r\nC) Hydraulic schematic\r\nD) Block diagram",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Fundamentals-QX.57-30179552-ASMrevV.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "58",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Advise what type of drawing this is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Assembly Drawing\r\nB) Manufacturing Drawing\r\nC) Hydraulic schematic\r\nD) Part specification Drawing",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Fundamentals-QX.58-118632-ASMrevD.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "59",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Given the thread external diameter is measured to be 0.562” and the threads per inch is measured at 18, confirm the thread series",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 9/16” UNC\r\nB) 5/8” UNF                                                                 C) 9/16\" UNF\r\nD) M14",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.59-Zeusbook.pdf",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "61",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "From the Hexagonal head bolt details shown in the attachment of this question, confirm the fastener grade.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Grade 5                                                                 B) Grade 8\r\nC) Grade 8.8\r\nD) Grade 2",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.61-question2.pdf",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "67",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "For a nut located in a high vibration area, select the preferred type.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Hex Nut\r\nB) Wing Nut\r\nC) low callor Nut                                                      \r\nD) Castle Nut",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "75",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The bolt shown in the attachment of this question is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Class 8.8\r\nB) Grade 8\r\nC) Grade 5\r\nD) Class 5.8",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.75-Bolt.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "76",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The bolt shown in the attachment of this question is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Class 8.8\r\nB) Grade 8\r\nC) Grade 5\r\nD) Class 5.9",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.76-Bolt.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "77",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the thread series used to classify fine screw threads.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) UNC\r\nB) UNF\r\nC) UNEF\r\nD) Pitch",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "78",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the thread series used to classify coarse screw threads.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) UNC\r\nB) UNF\r\nC) UNEF\r\nD) Major Diameter",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "80",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Retention",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using a length of engagement of 1.5 x D, what would the required length of engagement be for a 1/2” screw be?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 7/8\"\r\nB) 3/4\"\r\nC) 5/8\"\r\nD) 3/16\"",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "84",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Torquing",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What method(s) can be used for tightening / torquing large diameter bolts?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Hydraulic Tensioner\r\nB) Turn of the Nut Method\r\nC) Hydraulic Torque wrench\r\nD) All above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "92",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the true statement.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Orientation of a lip seal should be, lip facing the cavity required to be sealed                                                   B) Orientation of a lip seal should be, lip facing away from the cavity required to be sealed\r\nC) Orientation of a lip seal is not critical successful sealing\r\nD) Depending on orientation the seal should be removed ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "95",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The purpose of a back-up ring on an O-Ring seal is to",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Provide a back-up seal                                            B) Maintain the O-Ring shape and position\r\nC) It has no purpose\r\nD) Provides a better seal  ",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "97",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "On a typical cylinder assembly mounted in front of the pressure seal you would have a",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Backup seal                                                           B) Wiper Seal\r\nC) Packing seal\r\nD) O-ring seal",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "98",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The seal shown in the attached image is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Lip Seal\r\nB) Scraper \r\nC) O-ring\r\nD) Mechanical seal",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Seal",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "99",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The seal shown in the attached image is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Lip Seal\r\nB) Scraper \r\nC) O-ring\r\nD) Mechanical seal",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Seal",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "104",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When installing an O-Ring with a back-up ring, the back-up ring ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) The back-up ring should be in front of the pressure side. \r\nB) The O-Ring is installed in front of pressure side and back-up ring is behind.\r\nC) The position of the back-up ring and the O-Ring does not matter.\r\nD) It is always necessary to have one back-up ring in front and another back-up ring at the back.",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "105",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the correct position/orientation to install a lip seal?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Facing the lip towards the oil / grease to retain it.\r\nB) Face the lip towards the contaminants to avoid its ingress.\r\nC) Can be assembled in combination, in oposite to retain the oil / grease and other seal to avoid contaminants ingress. Usually these combination is separated by grease chamber or spacer ring. \r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "106",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "To assemble the seals of the attached drawing, you need:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Coat the channel with grease, place the O-Ring, heat the seal up to 300ºF and assemble it, taking care about distortion when the seal is shrinking.\r\nB) Install the O-Ring and cover with grease, heat the seal up to 300ºF and assemble it.\r\nC)  Fill the channel with grease, place the O-Ring, heat the seal up to 300ºF and assemble it, taking care about distortion when the seal is shrinking.\r\nD)  Install the O-Ring, heat the seal up to 260ºF and assemble it.\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Gaskets&Seals-Installation-QX.106-2034295rev0.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "113",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The coupling shown in the attached image is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Flexible coupling\r\nB) Ridgid coupling\r\nC) Gear type coupling.\r\nD) Flange type",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "DriveComponents-Type-QX.113-Coupling.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "114",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The correct way to inspect the chain is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Check the sag out of chain in the sprocket.\r\nB) Check the chain elongation.\r\nC) Check for damage in the links of chain and wear evidence in the top of sprocket teeth.\r\nD) All Above.",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "116",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The correct parameters for gear alignment are:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Adjusting the backlash\r\nB) Adjusting the gear contact using adjustment paste/layout fluid.\r\nC) Confirming the contact pattern described in the user manual.\r\nD) All Above.",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "117",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What are the correct ways to check the backlash of a gear?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Feeler gauge, Strain Gauge, micrometer.\r\nB) Dial indicator, Feeler Gauge, lead wire.\r\nC) Calliper, strain gauge, dial indicator.\r\nD) Feeler Gauge, dial indicator, micrometer.",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "123",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the purpose of “backlash” between drive gears",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) To accommodate manufacturing tolerance, thermal expansion and lubricate                                               B) Prevent excessive noise from the drive train\r\nC) To prevent high load during initial rotation of the drive train\r\nD) To aid with initial installation ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)\r\n",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "128",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A driven gear being 40 teeth and driver being 20, select the correct gear ratio",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 40:20                                                                        B) 2:1\r\nC) 1:2\r\nD) 1/2",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "129",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "From the listed ratios, select the ratio that gives the highest output torque",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 1:5\r\nB) 4:1\r\nC) 1:1                                                                           D) 5:1",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "134",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "For a bearing located in a high speed rotating application select the best suited bearing type",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Bronze bush                                                          B) Ball bearing\r\nC) Nylon Bush\r\nD) Needle roller bearing ",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "138",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the most unsuitable method of applying heat to bearing race to assist with installation",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Oil bath\r\nB) Induction heater\r\nC) Blow torch                                                               D) Oven",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "139",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Spalling of a bearing race is where ",
            "Answer alternatives": "\r\nA) The races are in good condition\r\nB) The bearing is worn but in a good running condition  C) The bearing race is flaking material and poor condition \r\nD) The bearing requires lubrication \r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "140",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Why is a Needle bearing  used instead of a roller bearing?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) This bearing carry more load\r\nB) When you have limited mount spaceDue \r\nC) Due the possibility to be use directly in the shaft without the inner race\r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "141",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Tapered roller bearings are commomnly used on Crown block and traveling blocks. What is the reason to use this type of bearing?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Due the high load.\r\nB) Due the axial and radial load combination,\r\nC) Due the high axial load\r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "142",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Why are rolling bearings used instead of plain bearings?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) They have lower friction coeficient.\r\nB) Higher speeds are allowed\r\nC) They save power during the transmission\r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "149",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In some assemblies the interference between the shaft and bearing is high. The best assembly method is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Heating the bearing in Hydraulic oil\r\nB) Heating the bearing with torch\r\nC) Heating the bearing with Induction heaters\r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "150",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The correct lubrificant for a bearing is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Gear Oil\r\nB) Hydraulic Oil\r\nC) Grease NLGI 2\r\nD) According to the manufacturer lube chart",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "151",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Avise all of the methods you can use to check the bearing clearance?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Feeler gauge\r\nB) Dial indicator \r\nC) Lead wire\r\nD) All Above",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                                B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "153",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In a typical lubrication system the lubricating oil runs back to the …….., before being recirculated",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Sprayers\r\nB) Sump                                                                     C) Drain\r\nD) Galleries",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "154",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "From the list of lubrication systems, select the type which does not include a pump",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Splash System                                                        B) Forced system\r\nC) Pumped system\r\nD) Spray system",
            "Correct Answer": "A)\r\n",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "156",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Advise a suitable gear oil for TDX-1250 running in ambient temperature of 20 degrees; VG_____",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) VG 100                                                                       B) VG 150                                                                     C) VG  320                                                                      D) VG 460",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Lubrication-Type-QX.156-RecommendedLubricantsGuideD811000719-PRO-001rev7.pdf",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "158",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "If a bearing is not enclosed within an operational housing a suitable lubrication would be",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Oil\r\nB) Grease                                                                  C) Nothing\r\nD) Molycote",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "159",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Filtration",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "From the list of micron rated filters, select the filter which will remove the smallest contamination particles ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 50um\r\nB) 80um                                                                      C) 30um\r\nD) 100um",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "160",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Filtration",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A strainer will be mounted at which part of the lubrication circuit",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Gearbox nozzles\r\nB) Divertor manifold                                                     C) Pump Suction\r\nD) Pump discharge",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "166",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The lubrication type when the shaft starts moving, or the load become higher than specified in project, or when the viscosity become very low is:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Boundary Lubrication\r\nB) Hydrodinamic lubrication\r\nC) Hydrostatic Lubrication\r\nD) Extreme pressure lubrication",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "167",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The type of lubrication when moving surfaces are separated by the pressure of a continuous unbroken film or layer of lubrication is called:",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Boundary Lubrication\r\nB) Hydrodinamic lubrication\r\nC) Hydrostatic Lubrication\r\nD) Extreme pressure lubrication",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "169",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The gear lubrication method where the gear is allowed to dip into the lubricant, carrying it around to the mesh is called.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Manual Lubrication\r\nB) Forced lubrication\r\nC) Splash or bath \r\nD) Extreme pressure lubrication",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "170",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The lubrication method where a pump is used to force the oil through the componentes or to spray is called",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Manual Lubrication\r\nB) Forced lubrication\r\nC) Splash or bath \r\nD) Extreme pressure lubrication",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "177",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Please select  the correct gear oil from the list for a TDX Top Drive gearbox by using the Attached lubricant guide.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Texaco Rando HDZ 15\r\nB) Mobile Mobilith SCH 460\r\nC) Texaco Synlube WS 150\r\nD) Texaco Multifak EP2\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Lubrication-Type-QX.177-RecommendedLubricantsGuideD811000719-PRO-001rev7.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "182",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "During the Permit to work issue, you need to perform the risk assessment. What is main goal of Risk assessment?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Identify the potential risks in the specific task.\r\nB) Identify the resources required. to do the job.                                                                      C) Check if the tools and PPE you going to use are in good condition.                                                           D) All above.      ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "183",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Is a Risk Assessment carried out for every task?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "185",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When operating a needle gun, the operator should wear ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Eye Protection                                                              B) Safety Shoes                                                                        C) Hearing Protection                                                           D) Overalls                                                                              E) Gloves / Hand Protection                                                                    F) All the above",
            "Correct Answer": "F)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "186",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Explain why a piece of equipment that you are planning to work on should be Isolated, Locked Out and Tagged",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Permit to Work requirement\r\nB) Prevent its operation\r\nC) Ensures it is safe to work on                                      D) All of the above",
            "Correct Answer": "D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "187",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Explain the use of Secondary Retention",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Reduce the risk of dropped objects.                                                                       B) Stop it moving around.                                            C) Assist in its dis-assembly.                                       D) Make it look profesional.",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "188",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When carrying out a specific task, what are the best tools to be used?.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Whatever tools are available and at hand\r\nB) The correct tool for the job\r\nC) Any of the above",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "199",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using drawing # 10659959-DAD. Identify the type of drawing",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Assembly Drawing\r\nB) Manufacturing Drawing\r\nC) Hydraulic schematic\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Fundamentals-QX.199-10659959-DADrev05.pdf",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "200",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Fundamentals",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When seeing the following surface finish symbols on a drawing i.e. 32√, 63√, 125√, 250√,is the larger number the smoother surface finish.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "201",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What is the purpose of seals and gaskets?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) To prevent the escape of fluids from the assembly\r\nB) To prevent the ingress of foreign matter into the assembly                                                                   C) Both of the above",
            "Correct Answer": "C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "202",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the correct statement for a typical static seal.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) - There is no movement between the parts.                                                                     B) - There is movement between the parts.",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "203",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "If a driven shaft is mis-alignend from a drive shaft, what would be a common effect?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) High Vibration                                                        B) Excelerated Wear                                                    C) Increased noise levels                                            D) Premature Failure                                                  E) All of the above",
            "Correct Answer": "E)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "207",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using sketch Gear Ratio the drive gear has 20 teeth and the driven gear had 30 teeth. Determine the correct gear ratio",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 0.5:1\r\nB) 1.5:1\r\nC) 2.5:1",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "DriveComponents-Type-QX.207-Gearratio.pdf",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "212",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Which is the best type of lubricant to use for high speed componants.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Oil                                                                         B) Grease                                                                   C) Both",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "217",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Of the following tasks, indicate when safety glasses should be worn.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Filing.                                                                                    B) Drilling.                                                                                         C) Tapping.                                                                                   D) Grinding.                                                                          E) Hacksawing.                                                                           F) Reaming.                                                                         G) Chiselling.                                                                                   H) When warning Signs instruct you to.\r\nI) All of the above",
            "Correct Answer": "I)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "218",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Choice",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "What items of personal protection must be worn at all times when working on equipment on a rig.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Safety shoes, Eye protection, Overalls, Hard hat.                      B) Ear protection, Overalls, Hard hat.                                              C) Safety shoes, Overalls.                                                           D) Safety shoes, Ear protection, Overalls.",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                                                                                                                                                    ",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "0",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Which of the following two alternatives of stored energies is required to be released prior to work.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Belt Tension                                                                 B) Safety valves                                                                   C) System pressure                                                                 D) Oil reservoir",
            "Correct Answer": "C)                                      A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife",
            "Approved For Articulate?": "Ok",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "1",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "1",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Which two of the following alternatives is suitable means to carry out a mechanical isolation prior to work being carried out;",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Closing isolation valve                                                      B) Venting stored power                                                         C) Isolate electrical power supply                                        D) Release Tension",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                     B)                                                          ",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife",
            "Approved For Articulate?": "Ok",
            "Added to Articulate": "Ok",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "1",
            "Added to Articulate2": "1",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "7",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Assessment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When selecting a fall arrestor for working at height, in addition to checking the certification which other item should be checked",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Condition                                                               B) Applicability                                                                   \r\nC) Weight of the fall arrestor\r\nD) Expiry date ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                                     B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "22",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The torque wrench is one of the methods to achieve the desire pre-tensioning of bolts. Which other two methods is commonly by NOV used to control the torque.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Angle method (turn of nut)\r\nB) Impact wrench\r\nC) Hydraulic tensioner\r\nD) All of the above ",
            "Correct Answer": "A) C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "31",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Measuring",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Prior to use of a piece of measuring equipment, which five  checks from the list should be carried out.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Calibration\r\nB) Condition \r\nC) Operation                                                                 D) Brand\r\nE) Storage Method\r\nF) Suitability ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                      B)                                   C)                                    E)                                   F)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "32",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Power",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Prior to use of portable hydraulic / electric hand tools, please select the five checks that should be carried out before use.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Condition\r\nB) Operation\r\nC) Rating\r\nD) Training                                                                   E) Brand\r\nF) Maintenance",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                    B)                                    C)                                   D)                                    F)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "63",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Retention",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the three correct answers.\r\n“When tightening a fastener it is critical to apply the correct torque to the fastners to”",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Prevent damage to the fastner\r\nB) Create sufficient friction in the connection\r\nC) Prevent the nut loosening                                        D) Aid with the installation",
            "Correct Answer": "A)\r\nB) \r\nC)                                      ",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "68",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Retention",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "For a non through bolted connection select the two retention methods.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Lock wire\r\nB) cotter pin\r\nC) Adhesive compound                                                     D) castle nut",
            "Correct Answer": "A)\r\nC)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "89",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A typical example for a rotating shaft seal would be (two correct answers)",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Ceramic Seal                                                          B) Paper gasket\r\nC) Ring gasket                                                              D) Packing Seal",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                                              D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "121",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Which three answers is correct; Accurate coupling alignment is critical because",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Maximised lifecycle of the coupling\r\nB) No transferred stresses on drive motors etc\r\nC) Aids with rapid coupling replacement                          \r\nD) Smooth operation of the transmission",
            "Correct Answer": "A) \r\nB)                                              D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "124",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the three correct advantages of drive belt over drive chain",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Reduced noise\r\nB) Reduced maintenance\r\nC) Higher operating capacity\r\nD) Longer operating lifecycle\r\nE) Smooth operation ",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                            B)                                              E)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "132",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A bearing application is subject to high axial load, select the two bearing types that is suitable",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Ball Bearing\r\nB) Needle bearing                                                       C) Taper roller bearing\r\nD) Thrust bearing",
            "Correct Answer": "C)                                               D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "133",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The outer race of a taper roller bearing is to be installed in a bore with no clearance between bore and race. Select the two preferred methods to install bearing.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Apply heat to the bearing\r\nB) Cool the bore                                                          C) Cool the bearing                                                    D) Apply heat to bore",
            "Correct Answer": "C)                                               D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "135",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Select the two tools commonly used to measure bearing clearance ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Micrometer                                                           B) Feeler Gauge                                                         C) Dial Test Indicator \r\nD) Vernier",
            "Correct Answer": "B)                                                C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "136",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The two 1st line identification methods to establish a bearing is wearing would be ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Visual inspection                                                    B) Location                                                                C) Size \r\nD) Clearance",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                                       D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "162",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When carrying out a basic health check on a  lubrication system, select all of the five basic checks that should be carried out from the list of alternatives",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Oil Brand                                                               B) Lube oil Pressure\r\nC) Oil level\r\nD) Flow rate\r\nE) Consider Oil condition\r\nF) Lube filter by pas\r\nG) Pump condition ",
            "Correct Answer": "B)                                                C)                                           D)                                             E)                                          F)                                     ",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "194",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Measuring",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Why should we be using calibrated tools? (two correct answers)",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) It looks good infront of the customer.                           B) To make sure we are getting the correct readings.                                  C) To keep the measurement errors within acceptable levels.                                                                            D) All of the above.",
            "Correct Answer": "B)                                            C)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "197",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drawings",
            "Subtopic": "Interpret",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using page 3 of drawing # 30179552. Identify the balloon numbers of  the three bearings.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) 17                                                                         B) 9                                                                             C) 8                                                                           D) 51                                                                         E) 10                                                                          F) 52                                                                         G) 53",
            "Correct Answer": "B)                                            C)                                      E)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Drawings-Interpret-QX.197-30179552-ASMrevV.pdf",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        
        {
            "Question ID2": "211",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Using drawing # 30179552 (page 3) identify the the types of bearings used (8, 9, 10)",
            "Answer alternatives": "Main Thrust\r\nBronze bearing\r\nTapered Roller\r\nNeedle bearing\r\nCylindrical Roller",
            "Correct Answer": "Main Thrust\r\nTapered Roller\r\nCylindrical Roller",
            "Attachment(s)": "Bearings-Type-QX.211-30179552-ASMrevV.pdf",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "216",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "Multiple Response",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When using compressed air, which two things should be avoided?",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) Directing a jet of air at clothes, hair or any part of the body.                                                                                     B) Always use the lowest possible pressure for the job.                   C) Turn of the air supply before changing tools.                              D) Leaving the air gun unattended.                                           E) Ensure that the hose and fittings are working property.",
            "Correct Answer": "A)                                                D)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "146",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Text Input",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Needle bearings are used instead of ball bearings due to their high axial load capability.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) Flase",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "173",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "Text Input",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "If the oil is from same brand but different grade, the compatibility should be verified prior to mixing",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "2",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "For working at height all tools need to be retained",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                         B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife",
            "Approved For Articulate?": "Ok",
            "Added to Articulate": "Ok",
            "Pedagogic Approved": "Ok",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "1",
            "Added to Articulate2": "1",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "1",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "5",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Fabrication of tools is acceptable when the correct tool for the job is not available",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                        B) False               ",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "13",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "“Lockout” means “the placement of a tagout device on an energy-isolating device to indicate that the device and the equipment being controlled may not be operated until the tagout device is removed”.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "14",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A “tagout device” is any prominent warning device, such as a tag and a means of attachment, that can be securely fastened to an energy-isolating device to indicate that the machine or equipment to which it is attached may not be operated until the tagout device is removed.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "17",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Standards",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The locking of bolts in order to secure against loss of pre-load (tension) is defined as secondary retention.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "18",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Health & Safety",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Double Nut / Dual Nutting is the only secondary retention method in the industry.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "35",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Tools",
            "Subtopic": "Hand",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When a correctly sized combination spanner is available the preference is to use an adjustable wrench ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                        B) False               ",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "66",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Lubricant",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Does  lubrication to the threads influence the torque needed to secure the fastener according to specification",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "70",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The bolt showed in the attachement of this question is a countersunk bolt.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.70-Bolt.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "72",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The screw head in the attachment of this question is Phillips.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.72-Screw.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "73",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Nuts are used on Non-through Bolts.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "74",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The Nut Shown in the attachment of this question is an anco nut.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Fasteners-Type-QX.74-Anco-Lock-Nut.pdf",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "79",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Imperial Bolts specify the diameter and pitch, while metric bolts specify the diameter and number of threads per specific length.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "81",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Retention",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Norlock type washers have better performance than spring washer under vibration conditions.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "82",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Retention",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Castle nut and slotted nut are commonly used on NOV equipment with cotter pin for secundary retention.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "83",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Lubricant",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Is the torque value dependent on the type of lubricant being used on the threads",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "86",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Torquing",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Hydraulic bolt tensioners can always be used to tension small bolts.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "88",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Fasteners",
            "Subtopic": "Torquing",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The advantage of using a torque multiplier is that you have more force to overcome the friction forces of threads.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "90",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The function of a seal or gasket is only to prevent a liquid escaping from a transit duct. ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                        B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "91",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Orientation of a lip seal installation is critical to the successful operation and life cycle.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                        B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "93",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When a gasket material is being selected it is essential to consider the medium being transmitted.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                        B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "94",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Lubrication of a lip seal is required to ensure the lifecycle of the seal is as intended.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                        B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "102",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Back-up Rings have no intended sealing function. Instead,\r\nas their name indicates, they are protective and supporting\r\nelements made from extrusion-resistant materials which\r\ngenerally have a rectangular cross section.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "107",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The assembly method shown in the Image is correct.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "Seal",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "109",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "\"Soft foot\" does not have an influence in the final alignment.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "110",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Pulleys & Belts",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Timing Belts are used to transfer power from primer mover to a moved device.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "111",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Alignment",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The belt alignment tolerance depends on belt type and distance between the center of sheaves.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "112",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Flexible couplings can accomodate more misalignment than rigid couplings.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "115",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Offset links (half link) are used to connect a chain when the standard link is too long.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "127",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Drive Components",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A dynamic braking system will be used to reduce the travelling speed of something",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                               B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "137",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "A needle roller bearing has a higher loading capacity than a roller bearing",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                      B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "143",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Plain bearings are used in sliding applications as slide bearings",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) Flase",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "144",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Because of their greater contact area and conformability, plain bearings provide higher load capacity and resistance to high shock loads and edge loading",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) Flase",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "145",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Plain bearings can operate dry at high temperatures and with the presence of contaminants",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) Flase",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "147",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The correct way to assemble a bearing on the shaft is pressing or tapping the outer race until  the bearing fits on the shaft.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "148",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Installation",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "The correct way to assemble the bearing in the housing or cage is pressing or tapping the outer race with brass or dead blow hammer.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "152",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Bearings",
            "Subtopic": "Maintenance",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "If the bearing presents any pitting in the rolling race, an evaluation and planning should be put in place immediately for replacement.  ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "155",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "In a warmer climate the oil Viscosity grade would be higher ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                      B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "157",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "It is acceptable to mix mineral and synthetic oils ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                      B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "161",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Filtration",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "When filling a lubrication circuit direct from a manufacture’s supply, the oil should be filtered during filling ",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True                                                                      B) False",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Andrew Scaife"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "163",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Grease is basically composed of base oil, thickner and aditives.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "164",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Grease usually has  between 70 and 95% of base oil in its composition.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "165",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Grease NLGI 1 is thicker than NLGI 2",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "171",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "It is not recommended to combine grease from different brands or base oil",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "172",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "It is possible to mix lubrication oil from different brands since they have the same viscosity and viscousity index.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "174",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "Improper lubrication is the biggest cause of bearing failure.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "175",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Method",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "If the lubrication system is sealed aginst foreign contaminants you don't need to worry about filtration",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "A)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Mike Horiansky"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "178",
            "Level": "0",
            "Topic": "Lubrication",
            "Subtopic": "Type",
            "QuestionType": "True / False",
            "Theoretical /Code used": "Theoretical",
            "Question": "To lubricate the motor bearing you need to use Shell Cyprina grease.",
            "Answer alternatives": "A) True\r\nB) False\r\n",
            "Correct Answer": "B)",
            "Attachment(s)": "N/A",
            "Creator": "Hudson Carvalho"
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "220",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "221",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "222",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "223",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "224",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "225",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "226",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "227",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "228",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "229",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "230",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "231",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "232",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "233",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "234",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "235",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "236",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "237",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "238",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "239",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "240",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "241",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "242",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "243",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "244",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "245",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "246",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "247",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "248",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "249",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "250",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "251",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "252",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "253",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "254",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "255",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "256",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "257",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "258",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "259",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Question ID2": "260",
            "Level": "X",
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        },
        {
            "Approved For Articulate2": "",
            "Added to Articulate2": "",
            "Pedagogic Approved2": "",
            "Approved in Articulate2": ""
        }
    ],
    "Pivot": [
        {
            "Count of Question": "Topic",
            "undefined": "Total"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Bearings",
            "undefined": "6"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "5"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "13"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Bearings Total",
            "undefined": "24"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Drawings",
            "undefined": "11"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "7"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "3"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "4"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Drawings Total",
            "undefined": "25"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Drive Components",
            "undefined": "7"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "5"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "1"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "19"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Drive Components Total",
            "undefined": "32"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Fasteners",
            "undefined": "3"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "5"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "5"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "17"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Fasteners Total",
            "undefined": "30"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Gaskets & Seals",
            "undefined": "11"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "10"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Gaskets & Seals Total",
            "undefined": "21"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Health & Safety",
            "undefined": "7"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "4"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "17"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Health & Safety Total",
            "undefined": "28"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Lubrication",
            "undefined": "4"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "11"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "16"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Lubrication Total",
            "undefined": "31"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Tools",
            "undefined": "15"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "11"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "2"
        },
        {
            "undefined": "1"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Tools Total",
            "undefined": "29"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "(blank)"
        },
        {
            "Count of Question": "Grand Total",
            "undefined": "220"
        }]
}
module.exports = jsondata;